net4domains.com 2019-06-24

# Privacy Policy - Net4

**WHOIS:** We are required by the Internet Corporation for Assigned Names and Numbers ("ICANN"), the organization that assumes responsibility for domain name allocation, to collect information about you during the domain name registration process. This information includes your full name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and, where provided, your facsimile number. ICANN then requires all registrars to make your full name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and, where provided, your facsimile number, as well as the creation and expiration dates of your domain name registration and the name server information associated with your domain name, to the public via an interactive web page and a "port 43" WHOIS service. For the purposes of this Privacy Notice we will refer to this information as your "WHOIS Information". 

Please note that we may not be able to control how members of the public may use the WHOIS Information. If you have opted-into having your WHOIS Information available for bulk access, ICANN also requires Net4 to make that information available to third parties who enter into a bulk WHOIS data access agreement with Net4. In making your selection to opt-into having your WHOIS Information available for bulk access, please refer to Bulk WHOIS data policy information. Please note that if you have not opted-into having your WHOIS Information available for bulk access for marketing or other purposes, your WHOIS Information will still be made available to the public through the "port 43" WHOIS service described above. 

Except as set out in this Privacy Notice, you will receive notice when personal information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to have us share that information. We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Net4 under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Net4 communicate with you about offers from Net4 and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. We share personal information as described below: 

**Agents:** We engage other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include providing marketing assistance, providing customer services, sending postal mail and email to you, removing repetitive information from customer lists, and analyzing data. These persons have access to personal information needed to perform their functions. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information that you provide to A Mountain Domains for any secondary purposes. 

**Providers:** We engage other companies and individuals to perform enhanced services on our behalf. Many of our service providers have access to personal information needed to perform their services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 

**Business Transfers:** As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or their assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, if Net4 or all or substantially all of its assets were ever to be acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets. 

**Protection of Net4 and Others:** We release account and other personal information when we believe release is: (i) appropriate to comply with the law of the land; (ii) necessary for compliance with any legal summons, notices, orders, enquiries by law enforcement officials/ quasi-judicial forces; (iii) enforce or apply our Services Agreement and other agreements; (iv) or protect the rights, property, or safety of Net4, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

**Advertisers:** We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. Partners: We partner with other parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. 

**Compliance:** We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Services Agreement and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Net4, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
